



# <PUNG KUI SIN>

666 Woodlands Ring Road, Singapore 730666

pungkuisin@hotmail.com +6581363604 bit.ly/pung-portfolio

As a dedicated Web Developer with 3 years of experience, I specialize in creating robust and user-friendly websites and applications. My expertise spans frontend and backend technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and various CMS platforms.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Web Developer**

Germs Digital August 2022 - Present

- Deliver a comprehensive migration project, transferring over 500 pages via CMS for one of Singapore's top three banks.
- Develop and implement features and functionalities for both new and existing websites and applications using different programming languages like React JS, Jquery, Javascript, Bootstrap and PHP.

#### Webmaster

Webscape Consulting Oct 2018 - June 2022

Developed, updated websites, eDMs and new component releases, ensuring smooth integration into test and production environments.

#### **Software Engineering Intern**

CTC Integrated Software Engineering March 2018 - June 2018

Completed 3-month undergraduate trainee program. Developed a car seat demo website, created company websites using WordPress, and utilized Microsoft FoxPro to create a data conversion application program.

# **PROJECTS**

- Revamped and delivered a comprehensive 500-page CMS project
- Homestay reservation website and app
- Created and enhanced CMS components to improve functionality and user experience

## **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of IT (Hons) Security Technology

Multimedia University Malacca Malaysia 2015 - 2018 First Class Honors with a CGPA of 3.8

## **Diploma in Information Technology**

Multimedia University Malacca Malaysia 2013 - 2015 First Class Honors with a CGPA of 3.9

## SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, Vue JS, Bootstrap, PHP, Android Studio, MySQL, Java, C, C++
- OpenText TeamSite, AEM, Voyager, Wordpress
- GitHub, GitLab, Source Tree
- Microsoft products

#### LANGUAGES

English, Mandarin, Malay, Cantonese